(Sheldon:)Four glasses of water, please.
(Sheldon:)Anything for you guys?
(Leonard:)Can I use your phone?
Our car got stolen.
(Waitress:)Why don't you ask Scotty
to beam you up?
(Sheldon:)Scotty was on the original series
and we're Next Generation.
(Sheldon:)So joke's on you.
(Howard:)We're not with him.
(Amy:)You can't pick something up
in outer space.
(Amy:)In space, there is no up.
(Penny:)Oh, yeah? Then how does
the sun come up every day?
(Amy:)Hard to argue
with those kind of street smarts.
(Bernadette:)Leonard and Sheldon have boxes of comics.
Why don't we go look at those?
Oh, great. And then you will see,
I am not wrong.
(Penny:)If we were in outer space,
anyone could pick up the hammer...